If students are placed in the academic English preparation program
如果學生被安排在AEP學術英語預備課程，
the amount of time these students will spend in AEP varies.
這些學生在AEP上花費的時間會因為個別差異而有所不同。
Students placed in level one will complete the AEP program in four, five or six terms.
安排在AEP第一級的學生將以四、五或六個學期完成AEP課程。
Students placed in level two will complete the AEP program in three, four or five terms.
第二級學生將以三、四或五個學期完成AEP課程。
In Level three, they will complete the AEP program in two, three or four terms.
第三級學生，他們將以兩、三或四個學期完成AEP課程。
And in level four they will complete the program in one or two terms
而在第四級的學生，他們將以一、兩個學期完成該AEP課程計劃。
Students who arrive with very weak English will take longer,
通常，到校時英語水平較弱的學生，需要更長的時間。
Students who study hard speak English a lot
努力學習、常說英語、
and read English books will progress faster.
及常閱讀英文書籍的學生會進步得更快。
Students who participate extracurricular programs
多參加課外活動
and interact with students from other countries will progress faster
及與來自其他國家的學生進行互動的學生也會進步得更快。
All students arrive at Bodwell with different English experiences
所有學生抵達Bodwell時，英語實際經驗皆大相逕庭。
some students have learned a little English before arriving
有些學生在抵達前已經學會了一點英語，
but have never practiced it.
但從未實際練習過。
Some students have studied English for many years in their home countries
有些學生在母國學習英語多年，
or have studied English in other countries other before arriving at Bodwell.
或者在到達Bodwell之前在其他國家學習過英語。
Some students have completed high school courses
有些學生已經在加拿大的公立學校
at a Canadian public school.
完成了高中課程。
It's very important for students that wish to progress through the AEP program
希望盡早通過AEP課程並準備好常規課程的學生，
that they get involved and they use English
就是盡量地利用機會參與課外活動
as much as they can outside of the classroom.
和盡可能在課堂之外使用英語。
There's many opportunities
學生其實有很多課外機會使用及練習英語，
such as our Saturday enrichment program
比如在週六上午的加強課程、
our study Hall sessions with our tutors, our clubs,
在晚上有輔導老師協助的自修時間、
volunteer opportunities
也可以透過參加志工服務
and daily life where they speak
或在日常生活中
all of these things help students progress through the AEP program
所有這些都能幫助學生通過AEP課程獲得進步，
and get ready, have those essential skills
並做好準備。擁有這些基礎英文能力，
needed for academic success.
距離成功就不遠了。
Older students age 17, with weak English
年齡在17歲以上而英語水平較差的學生，
struggle to complete the AEP program
但必須在他們到達18或19歲之前完成AEP計劃
and the regular academic program
和正規學術課程，
before they reach the age of 18  or 19
確實是一場搏鬥。
Younger students must learn English,
年輕的學生必須同時學習英語
life skills and become mature all at the same time.
和基本生活技能，並且變得更成熟。
Young students progress at different rates.
不過，年輕學生進步的速度也會不同。